Finding aid to the Alexander C. Sanger papers SSC.MS.00654
Sophia Smith Collection
- AV Material, 1990-2012; 8
  - Video Cassettes, F
    - Planned Parenthood Tapes 1-4, 1995; 4 items (4 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Planned Parenthood Tapes 1-3, 1996; 3 items (3 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Planned Parenthood Tapes 1-2, 1997; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Planned Parenthood tapes 1-2, 1998; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Planned Parenthood tape 1, 1999; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Good Day; CBS-TV Sunday Edition; Today Show, January 28th, 1991; April 26th, 1992; 1994; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 93)
    - Fighting For the Future - Planned Parenthood of New York City, 1992; 3 items (3 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - NBC News; CBS News; ABC News; Fox 5 Good Day; Ch5; Ch2, June 29th, 1992; October 1st, 1992; June 30th, 1992; October 2nd, 1992; November 6th, 1992; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 93)
    - Alex Sanger - 3rd and 4th Quarter, 1993; 2 items (2 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - Planned Parenthood - Tennis-Dinkins, January 15th, 1993; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - Ceremony to Overturn "Gag Rule", January 22nd, 1993; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - "Planned Parenthood" - Local New York, Network Coverage, January 22-23, 1993; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - Sanger Footage in PPFA Library (Today) and NBC Evening News, 1994; 1993; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - "Who Decides?" - Nelson Bakerman Productions, 1994; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - Planned Parenthood - A Family Gathering, May 18, 1994; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 93)
    - Planned Parenthood League Massachusetts, April 5, 1995; 1 items (VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Alexander C.Sanger Keynote Address - Planned Parenthood League of Massachusetts, April 5, 1995; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Under Scrutiny Norplant Class Action Society, July 12, 1995; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - "Condoms in the Classroom", December 20, 1995; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - Choice Thoughts - Reflections on the Birth Control War, 1996; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - Alexander C. Sanger - Selected News Clips, January 11, 1996; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - ACS TV Clips, January 1996 - June 1996; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)
    - ACS TV - MSNBC: Various Including: New York Close Up; Good Day, September 11, 1996; September 18, 1996; 1996-09-19; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - "Booksellers" - Market Wrap - CNBC-TV Network, December 23, 1996; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Passing Through - Flint, Mich, May 8, 1997; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Alexander C. Sanger - 50th Video, October 1997; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - 100 Years of Healing - Healthweek@Maryland Public Television, December 1997; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 91)
    - Capital Campaign Luncheon with Doris Kearns Goodwin, April 6, 1998; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Alex Sanger - Perspective #1230, March 2000; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 91)
    - WQPT - Alex Sanger, March 2000; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 91)
    - Feminist Expo 2020 - General Assembly I - Tapes 1 and 2, March 31, 2000; 2 items (2 VHS videocassette) (Box 91, Box 93)
    - Planned Parenthood Golden Gate (raw footage and finished material), October 17, 2000; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 91)
    - SJ Roe v. Wade Event with Alex Sanger, January 27, 2001; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 91)
    - Saving Women's Lives (CBS - KTVT Ch. 11), November 3, 2001; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 91)
    - Alexander Sanger - Author of Beyond Choice - The O'Reilly Factor, January 20, 2004; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Ben Cheever TV Show, May 10, 2004; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Alex Sanger "Planned Parenthood" - Clemson University Communications Center, October 11, 2004; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - "Women Aloud" - Show #314 - Lizz Winstead, Dr. Susan Wicklund, Alexander Sanger, undated; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 91)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City - A Social Contract: The Abortion Provider Crisis, undated; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 91)
    - "Keeping The Promise" - Planned Parenthood of the Rochester/Syracuse Region, undated; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 91)
    - Comedy Central - Women Aloud - "Doctors Who Perform Abortions", undated; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City. Inc - platform principles, commercials, undated; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - PSAs: "Birth Control: Try It. It Works.", undated; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - ACS Book Events - O'Reilly, undated; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City - "Here to Help", undated; 2 items (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 93)
    - Margaret Sanger Interview - tapes 1-3, undated; 3 items (3 VHS videocassettes) (Box 93)
    - Flint, Michigan - Passing Through, May 8, 1997; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City - "Here to Help", 1992; 1 items (1 VHS videocassettes) (Box 92)
  - Floppy Disks, G
    - PP North Texas, April 7th, 2000; 1 items (1 floppy disk) (Box 92)
    - People Count, 1997; 1 items (1 floppy disk) (Box 92)
    - "In Search of Cal Ripkin in Beijing", 1997; 1 items (1 floppy disk) (Box 92)
    - Alex Sanger Bio., 1 items (1 floppy disk)